[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 8]
Senior.
Have some water.
Senior...
What's wrong with you?
Are you all right, senior?
I'm fine.
Leave me alone.
You can off to go.
Senior,
I have something to ask you.
Lu Li.
What's the matter?
How do you
explain the fire in the Pearl Pavilion?
This matter has been conclusively attributed
to the grass demon.
You're still suspecting me?
I'm so sad about this.
I'm sad too.
Senior.
It seems that time would really change a person.
Listen to yourself.
What have I changed?
Actually, you're the one who has been changing.
We grew up together.
Master's way of educating us
was to leave us in the barren mountains
and let us live on our own abilities.
So we had to learn to be ruthless
and tough.
But do you remember
that we agreed
not to kill innocent people?
Of course I do.
So how are you going to explain the fire in Pearl Pavilion?
If it wasn't because I and Liu Shao's spiritual power restrained each other,
and we had special physical constitutions,
and if I hadn't arrived at the scene in time,
the demon fire would have killed her.
What if
I just meant to kill her?
Senior.
I will protect her
with my life.
Don't make me hate you.
Lu Li.
You won't kill me.
Beacuse you're too affectionate.
You've been pretending to be cruel.
Stop acting tough.
The demon fire belongs to Ao Hen,
and that mark belongs to you.
You should know what will happen to you
if I tell master about this,
right?
Master is different from me.
No matter who that person is,
no matter how close that person is to him,
he won't care.
Lu Li.
You won't do that.
You always say I've changed.
Maybe you're right.
I will do anything
for Liu Shao.
I know you don't want to see me like that,
and neither do I.
Captain Fang.
How is the Lord's refinement going?
It seems to be going well.
The Lord is saved.
And the human world is saved too.
That's good.
Done?
Yep.
What's wrong, My Lord?
My Lord!
Wan Sui took the blame for this?
I think it
must have something to do with Bai Feng
and Du Mingchong.
Liu Shao.
I want to pull out the Moon Sword.
Okay.
I'll help you.
You are not asking why?
You told me
that you wanted the mighty power of the Moon Sword
to counter those machinations
and protect the people you wanted to protect.
You want to protect me.
You want me to stop being afraid of Ao Hen
even after I leave Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
I told you
I would take you home.
You will eventually leave Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
and go home.
But
I have a request.
Even if you gain great power,
and I continue to hire you to protect me, but you can't...
You can't overcharge me.
You're right.
I charged you 30,000 taels of silver before,
but I forgot to mention the time limit.
What... You want to increase the price?
Then I'll set a time limit
until
the day I can't protect you anymore.
What day is that?
The day I can't protect a loved one
the day I am no longer needed,
and the day my life comes to an end.
That day will not come.
And even if it does,
I will protect you.
But
who is the loved one you mentioned just now?
Liu Shao.
In fact, there is another reason
why I want to pull out the Moon Sword.
I want to figure out my background.
Your background?
It was my master
who asked me to come to Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
And Bai Feng…
Here they are!
Hurry!
-Hurry! -Hurry!
Go.
Hurry up!
Look what you've done.
What are you talking about?
What happened to the Lord?
The Lord has treated you well.
Why did you put poison on King Herb to kill him?
What? We didn't do it.
Captain Fang,
Are you sure the King Herb was poisoned?
The Lord started to refine King Herb soon after he got it,
and there was nothing unusual during that time.
If King Herb didn't cause it, then what else could it be?
Captain Fang.
Think about it.
Liu Shao worked so hard to obtain King Herb
because she wanted to use it
to gain a foothold here.
At this time, the Lord was suddenly poisoned,
and all his disciples lost their protection,
which was not good news for Liu Shao.
Right. I'd be hunted by Ao Hen if I left here.
I really want the Lord to live a long life.
How could I try to kill the Lord?
It can't be them.
-Right. -How could she try to kill the lord?
That's right.
It can't be them.
Yes.
We may not know her at all.
I also don't think Liu Shao
would do it.
What about
the grass demon who gave us this King Herb?
Right.
King Herb is so precious.
Why did that grass demon give it to you so easily?
There must be a conspiracy.
That grass demon itself is the King Herb.
It's from the Immortal Palace and now has come back.
Are you going to say
that people from the Immortal Palace harmed the Lord?
No matter who was trying to kill the Lord,
there must have been something wrong with your King Herb.
We can only hold you accountable.
There is still half of the King Herb unrefined.
I will find a doctor to verify
what has been done to it.
But it was presented by you two.
This matter is definitely related to you.
My Lord.
-My Lord. -My Lord.
Captain Fang.
What do we do with these two villains?
I'll leave them to you.
Yes.
Behave yourself.
Lu Li.
Your cell is over there.
Don't be afraid.
The truth will come out soon.
I promised that I would take you home.
Trust me.
Okay.
Lu Li.
I trust you.
But this time even Marquis Wuyang has been poisoned.
How do we break the deadlock?
Lu Li.
I told you
not to be with her.
Not only did she fail to achieve anything,
but she also dragged you into troubles.
You knew
Liu Shao and I are innocent, right?
Whether you are innocent or not
is up to Du.
Why does Du have the final say?
Shouldn't it depend on the truth?
Neither Marquis Wuyang nor Captain Fang can be in charge.
If Du says it's truth,
then it is.
There is not only Du in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion,
but also you.
I didn't expect
you would become so vicious one day,
that you would kill innocent people for selfish reasons.
Innocent?
Am I not innocent?
You're hurting me by protecting Liu Shao.
What does it have to do with you?
You are my senior.
You've always been my senior.
I was not just your senior.
It's all Liu Shao's fault.
She caught your heart with her seductive look.
It's all her fault.
All.
I will make you
and her regret.
How is the Lord?
The physician said
this poison is too vicious.
It doesn't belong to the human world.
I'll use my vitality
to protect the Lord's heart.
That could buy us some time.
But if we still can't find the antidote,
the Lord won't last long.
What can I
do for the Lord?
Marquis Wuyang's Mansion needs someone to take charge.
You should take the responsibility now.
Manage the daily affairs of the Mansion
and find out the truth.
As long as the Lord is alive,
I will always be his disciple.
Let me do this instead.
It is my job to protect the Lord.
If you are really so sincere,
you should secure the Mansion
and find the cure for the Lord as soon as possible.
Yes.
I'll do as you say.
[Qiutian Pavilion]
[Wu]
Secure the cells and increase patrols.
No one is allowed to visit them.
You may leave.
Yes.
[Wu]
The Lord of the Human World
who rules all human beings
will soon be me.
Bai Feng?
Congratulations, Marquis Wuyang.
Don't talk nonsense.
The Lord is still alive.
I'm just a temporary replacement.
The throne is so comfortable.
Are you willing to give it up?
Bai Feng.
Watch your language.
What are you afraid of?
There's no one else here,
and no need to play ignorant.
Don't act like I don't know what you did.
I didn't do anything.
What do you want?
Nothing.
I'm just reminding you that
we will sink or swim together.
Don't try to kick down the ladder.
Otherwise, even if I die,
I will tell Captain Fang
what you did.
Senior Du,
I was just
reminding you.
As I said,
we will sink or swim together.
What exactly do you want?
I want Liu Shao dead,
and I will do it myself.
That's easy.
I want to keep Lu Li.
He and I have some unfinished business
to take care of.
It has nothing to do with yours.
Now,
you're going to take over Marquis Wuyang.
He is no longer a threat to you.
The matter of the Lord being poisoned has now been investigated clearly.
It was done by Liu Shao alone.
Lu Li was tricked and used by her,
and didn't know at first.
From now on, Lu Li is demoted to a lowly servant.
As for Liu Shao,
she will be left to Bai Feng
and executed immediately.
Execution?
-Execution? -Execution!
How can this be
so serious?
Nonsense! Liu Shao didn't...
Senior Du.
Please don't blame her.
Xue was blinded by Liu Shao and couldn't tell right from wrong.
I'll go back and teach her a lesson.
You better.
We don't need people who don't know any better.
Yes.
I... I'll take her back now.
Wang Jian, you...
Stop talking.
Let's go.
Xue, stop biting me.
You deserve it!
You ungrateful man.
Have you forgotten how Liu Shao helped me?
No, I haven't.
But it is Du in charge now.
We can't play tough with him.
Do you really want to be kicked out of the Mansion?
Do you have an idea?
Isn't Liu Shao going to be executed?
But my brother is fine.
He's just locked in prison.
They will definitely execute Liu Shao
before releasing him.
I know.
But we can go to him.
He's full of ideas.
My grandfather
had a few old friends in the Mansion.
They can't do anything else,
but it's not a problem for us
to visit him.
Brother.
Why are you here?
How are things outside?
Terrible.
The Lord is still unconscious.
Now Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
is basically under Du Mingchong's control.
Anyway, Bai Feng
doesn't look like a good person.
Xue is worried about Liu Shao.
It's useless to beg Bai Feng.
She will definitely kill Liu Shao.
In order to catch He Na,
she took Du to hurt Liu Shao.
I now get scared
every time I see her fake smile.
The fire in the Pearl Pavilion
must have something to do with her.
Help me find two people.
They should be able to help us.
Lu Li.
Lu Li!
I wonder how Lu Li is now.
I don't know what Bai Feng
will do with Liu Shao.
Lu Li.
What should we do now?
I have to get out of here as soon as possible
to save Liu Shao.
I hope Lu Li is fine.
Yes.
We'll all be fine.
Unlock the door.
Yes.
Your verdict has come out.
Don't you want to know?
I don't think it will be good news.
Lu Li said
that the King Herb
had been kept by you all the time.
He had never known that.
He also said
that you had been acting weird,
and were in contact with the demons.
Maybe you were bewitched by the demons
and asked them for poison to murder the Lord.
Because the evidence was solid,
Du has made his decision quickly.
Lu Li
was demoted to a lowly servant.
And you...
will be executed immediately.
This verdict
should be true.
But it must have been hard
for you to make up those lies.
I might have believed you,
if I didn't know anything about Lu Li.
You don't believe me?
Of course not.
Why not?
Because he's Lu Li,
and I'm Liu Shao.
You are really stuborn.
Fine.
Let's see if you still believe him
when you are about to die
and no one comes
to help you.
You know magic too?
You're right.
Actually, I basically know every magic
that Lu Li knows.
Do you wonder why?
Why?
Because I grew up with him,
and was meant to be with him.
I'm his senior.
Lu Sheng is also my master.
It seems he still has a lot of things
to hide from you.
He must have done that
for a reason.
I still trust him.
I knew it.
People who have never suffered
are really naive and ridiculous.
Naive people
live a simple, happy,
free and open life.
There is nothing to be proud of
living a hypocritical
and unstable life.
How dare you laugh at me?
I'm laughing at
those hypocrites.
What?
Are you also like this?
Fine.
Then I will be frank with you.
Let me tell you
how much I hate you,
and how much I want you to die.
Liu Shao,
enjoy it.
I'll make you suffer.
I want you to know the truth.
Lu Li was just using you
to help him pull out the Moon Sword.
The evil ones are usually the most pitiful.
Your heart is too vicious.
And you are deluded yourself that Lu Li will like you.
But everyone will hate you
when they see your hypocrisy.
You...
Ao Hen.
I've prepared what you wanted.
You're here.
I brought you Liu Shao.
Good.
Take it.
This demon energy is yours now.
But you'll have to figure out
how to absorb it for your own use.
I have one more request.
Go ahead.
Liu Shao has made me so angry,
and made you suffer so much.
You have to let her die in pain.
No problem.
If Lu Li and He Na knew
that the person they wanted to protect so much
couldn't even die as her wish,
how would they
react?
In that case,
just stay here and suffer.
Lu Li,
I have persuaded Senior Du to let you go.
But he had to
let me seal your Qihai first.
Don't you trust me?
Of course I trust you.
It might hurt a little, so bear with it.
Lu Li...
Be careful.
Sit here.
Are you feeling unwell?
I don't want this to happen too.
When this matter is over,
I will ask Senior Du
to unseal your Qihai acupoint.
Thank you so much.
Try this.
These are osmanthus cakes that I made myself.
You used to love it the most.
And I picked these osmanthus flowers myself.
These are really like the cakes you made when we were kids.
You used to want to eat this
every time you were sick.
I worked so hard to get osmanthus
so that you can eat osmanthus cakes again.
Yeah.
I still remember
that after I got well,
I fed the rest of the osmanthus cakes
to a parrot demon.
You pretended not to care at the time.
But then the parrot demon disappeared
and never appeared again.
You really
haven't changed since you were a kid.
You would always get
what you want.
You're selfish and unscrupulous.
Your Qihai acupoint is not sealed.
How could this be?
And it's not just that.
It's master's Psychedelic Amulet.
Yes.
I also asked Xue to send a message to master.
Help me find two people.
I told him you wanted to kill Liu Shao.
Give it to Lu Li.
That will trap Bai Feng for at least one tor two days.
Yes.
Liu Shao is dead.
You can't save her.
I once left a wisp of spiritual power
in Liu Shao's lake bead bracelet.
That way I could sense her life and death.
When can you
stop lying?
Okay.
Even if she is not dead,
what can you do?
She has been controlled by Ao Hen.
The great demon, Ao Hen.
Are you able to defeat her?
How do I know if I don't try?
Let me out!
Let's see how long you can last.
Liu Shao.
It's great that you're fine.
Run. Don't worry about me.
Liu Shao.
I won't leave you.
Your love is so touching.
Fine.
Then
I will fulfill you.
Lu Li!
Lu Li.
Lu Li, are you okay?
Just go. She just wants me.
Silly girl.
But I just want to save you.
Without Lu Sheng's help today,
let me see if you can escape.
Demon King in White?
He Na.
Demon King in White,
you've saved your people.
Why are you still against me?
They are my friends.
Friends?
You are a demon king.
How could you be friends with the disciples of Marquis Wuyang's Mansion?
Why not?
Nothing.
Just don't forget
that you are an Aquatic Demon.
In the water, you do have a distinguished status.
But now it's on land,
I'm the king here.
How long can you hold without water?
You want to protect them?
Water?
We have plenty.
Liu Shao.
Get up.
Is this little water
enough for you?
What if I use the Water Amulet my grandpa left me?
Watch carefully.
I will
spare them today.
I'd like to see
how long you can protect them.
Don't go.
There's more.
Are you okay?
He Na.
Thank you.
Thank you, kid.
Young man,
I heard that the Water Amulet has disappeared for almost a thousand years.
It wasn't Water Amulet.
That was the Thunder Amulet.
I just used it to create some illusions of lightning.
Why didn't you say it earlier?
Now is the best time to tell you.
That's not the point.
Let's go out first.
You can't go.
You must not go back.
Let's find a place to rest first.
Let's go.
Okay.
Liu Shao.
Thank you.
Mr. Tai is the best doctor in the demon world.
His prescription is very effective.
She will wake up
tomorrow.
You were also seriously injured.
Go back and take a rest.
I'm fine.
He Na.
Thank you
for helping us this time.
I didn't expect that Wang Jian really found you.
And you were really willing to take the risk to save us.
It's my fault.
I should have left her a way to find me.
Otherwise, she wouldn't be like this,
and couldn't even be able to tell me.
He Na.
From now on,
I will do my best to protect her.
I won't let anyone hurt her again.
I know.
But now,
you are not capable of doing so at all.
Soul-Devouring Spell
will make you die very quickly.
How long can you live?
Do you still have time?
My Lord.
Mr. Lu.
The spy at Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
gave me
a tuft of Marquis Wuyang's hair.
I've checked it.
Is it weird
that one or two greedy people in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion
became our spies?
No.
You get to know the enemy better this way.
Mr. Tai, please go ahead.
What hurt Marquis Wuyang was the demon poison.
It was most likely done by Ao Hen.
This poison is refined
by collecting the resentment of many people and demons.
I can't
cure this poison.
Now that Marquis Wuyang is sick,
the Marquis Wuyang's Mansion is controlled by Du Mingchong.
Then Liu Shao won't be able to prove her innocence.
How can she go back to the human world?
I will go to Ao Hen again
if there is no other way.
She must have the antidote.
But she won't come to the water.
And you can't defeat her on land.
How are you going to get the antidote?
I have to
give it a try.
Now that Marquis Wuyang is in a coma.
If anything bad happens to you,
then the three worlds will definitely be in chaos.
My Lord,
although I can't
deal with this poison,
there is one thing that can work.
[Marquis Wuyang's Mansion]
Be careful. Don't get caught.
Stop!
-Senior Du. -Senior Du.
Where have you been?
We
just went around the demon world.
Demon world?
What were you doing there?
We heard that the Lord has been poisoned by demon poison
and wanted to see if there was any clue.
Demon poison?
So did you find any clues?
We were walking there
and then we seemed to enter the territory of Ao Hen.
So we hurried back.
But
we saw pieces of clothes all over the place there.
All over the place.
So I brought one back.
This belongs to Liu Shao.
Yes, she's right.
Wait, Xue.
Wasn't Liu Shao already executed
by Senior Bai Feng?
How could she appear there?
That's right.
But she deserved it as a traitor.
Ao Hen?
How could Senior Bai Feng have anything to do with Ao Hen?
You must be wrong.
Don't slander and spread rumors casually.
You're right.
We must be wrong.
You can off to go now.
Yes, senior.
Lu Li.
You've been staring at this tree
for a long time.
I'm just waiting for a flower.
I heard from Mr. Tai
that a female flower from the Brahma tree
can cure all poisons in the demon world.
But I think
this tree is dead.
The old demon, He Na told me
that this tree died longer than he lived.
Old demon?
Yes.
He Na is old.
He is one thousand and one years old.
I am much younger than him.
This tree died before he was born.
He had never even seen the leaves of this tree,
and let alone the flowers.
I heard that Liu Shao had woken up,
so I brought wine to celebrate.
I heard you talking about me from a distance.
Did I say anything wrong?
Nothing.
In fact,
the Brahma tree has started to wither since 10,000 years ago.
The Water hyacinth that grows from the Brahma tree
has always existed only in the story.
But that poison
only left Marquis Wuyang a maximum of five days to live.
How do we make this tree,
which has been dead for 10,000 years,
bloom in five days?